<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://beerkay.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://beerkay.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to work on a number of interesting research projects during my Msc. and PhD. studies. I have developed new analysis tools and algorithms for emerging applications, built robust detection systems against sophisticated malware, designed new attacks for machine learning systems, and demonstrated the effectiveness of approaches on real systems. The system-specific core of my research has led to rewarding collaborations with researchers from program analysis, machine learning, networking, secure computation, and optimization. Here is a summary of some of my efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;iot-safety-security-and-privacy-analysis&#34;&gt;IoT Safety, Security, and Privacy Analysis&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have developed three systems, Soteria, IoTGuard, and Saint, to analyze IoT implementations and environments for safety, security and privacy, and a toolset for IoT analysis, IoTBench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/atc18/atc18-celik.pdf&#34;&gt;Soteria&lt;/a&gt; is a static analysis system to verify whether an IoT app or IoT environment (collection of apps working in concert) adheres to relevant safety, security, and functional properties. Soteria leverages the structured nature of IoT apps to extract a state model (finite state machine) of the IoT implementation by analyzing its source code. With Soteria, we demonstrated that many apps violate safety and security properties when used in isolation and when used together in multi-app environments. This work was presented in USENIX ATC&#39;18.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a more recent work, we have developed a second system called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndss-symposium.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/ndss2019_07A-1_Celik_paper.pdf&#34;&gt;IoTGuard&lt;/a&gt;, a dynamic system for policy enforcement on IoT devices. IoTGuard adds extra logic to an application source code to collect the application&amp;rsquo;s information at runtime. It then stores this information in a dynamic model that represents the runtime execution behavior of applications. Lastly, it enforces identified policies on the dynamic model of individual applications or sets of interacting applications. We designed two mechanisms to enforce these policies. The first mechanism blocks the device action(s) that causes the policy violation, and the second mechanism enables users to approve or deny the policy violation through runtime prompts. This work is recently accepted to NDSS&#39;19 and will be available online soon. Through Soteria and IoTGuard, we have demonstrated that policy-based validation and enforcement in physical spaces could be effectively realized in IoT and CPS systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third system is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity18/sec18-celik.pdf&#34;&gt;Saint&lt;/a&gt;, the first static taint tracking tool that finds sensitive data leaks in IoT applications by tracking information flows from taint sources (e.g., device state (door locked/unlocked)) to taint sinks (e.g., Internet and messaging services). Through this effort, we introduced a rigorously grounded framework for evaluating the use of sensitive information in IoT apps–and therein provide developers, markets, and consumers a means of identifying potential threats to security and privacy. This work appeared in USENIX Security Symposium&#39;18.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we have introduced &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/IoTBench/test-suite&#34;&gt;IoTBench&lt;/a&gt;, an IoT-specific test corpus for evaluating systems designed for IoT app analyses. IoTBench is under continual development and always welcoming contributions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My colleague, Xiaolei Wang and I created &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Beerkay/IoTResearch/blob/master/README.md&#34;&gt;a collection of papers&lt;/a&gt; we recommend reading for those interested in studying Internet of Things security and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt; 
&lt;img src=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/img/IoTResearch/saintTalk.png&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
[My Usenix Security&#39;18 talk on Sensitive Information Tracking in Commodity IoT](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ggsoDoOBdTo)
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;machine-learning-in-adversarial-settings&#34;&gt;Machine Learning in Adversarial Settings&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My collaborators and I investigated how existing training of Machine Learning (ML) models makes them vulnerable to adversarial samples (adversary-crafted inputs that result in misclassification). In our paper, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1511.07528.pdf&#34;&gt;The Limitations of Deep Learning in Adversarial Settings&lt;/a&gt;, we formalized the range of threat models on deep learning models and  developed a novel class of adversarial sample generation algorithms based on a precise understanding of the mapping between inputs and outputs of a deep neural network. In later work, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1602.02697.pdf&#34;&gt;Practical Black-Box Attacks against Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;,  my collaborators and I showed that the transferability of adversarial examples across models enables powerful black-box attacks: the adversary may use an auxiliary model to attack a victim model without access to model parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;robust-detection-models-under-privileged-information&#34;&gt;Robust Detection Models under Privileged Information&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Training of models has been historically limited to only those features available at runtime. In this effort, we ask &amp;ldquo;how can detection systems integrate intelligence relevant to an attack that is available at training time, yet not available at runtime?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider a rootkit detection system for mobile phones. Obtaining a set of features may drain the battery even though they contribute to the detection of a rootkit. Therefore, the users might disable the system because the battery dies very quickly. However, obtaining these features at training time is feasible as we have unlimited resources in a laboratory-based environment. We built an alternate model construction approach that trains models using &amp;ldquo;privileged&amp;rdquo; information&amp;ndash;features available at training time but not at runtime, yet samples are classified without the need of privileged features at runtime. Turning to rootkit example, the features draining the battery are the privileged features.  We showed that privileged information
increases precision and recall over a system with no privileged information, including in systems such as fast-flux bot detection, malware traffic detection,  malware classification, face recognition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our paper is accepted to ACM AsiaCCS&#39;18: &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1603.09638v4.pdf&#34;&gt;Detection under Privileged Information&lt;/a&gt;. Read more about its formulation and implementation in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://pdfs.semanticscholar.org/3637/5317aa86bea74df9505006377ca6e2ff3488.pdf&#34;&gt;technical report&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Celik17_CODASPY_IWSPA.pdf&#34;&gt;Feature Cultivation in Privileged Information-augmented Detection&lt;/a&gt; (invited paper in CODASPY IWSPA workshop).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;data-security-and-privacy&#34;&gt;Data Security and Privacy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users are asked to disclose personal information such as genetic markers, lifestyle habits, and clinical history that is used by statistical models to make accurate predictions in a wide array of applications, including medicine, law, forensics, and social networks.However, due to privacy concerns, users often desire to withhold sensitive information. This self-censorship can impede proper predictions. For instance, in health care models, it may lead to serious health complications. We have developed privacy distillation, a mechanism which allows users to control the type and amount of information they wish to disclose to the providers for use in statistical models. We evaluated privacy distillation in a healthcare model for warfarin dose prediction and found that with sufficient privacy-relevant information privacy distillation retains accuracy almost as good as having all patient data. The capacity afforded by this approach allows us to make accurate predictions in a wide array of applications requiring private inputs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1611.08648v1.pdf&#34;&gt;Patient-Driven Privacy Control through Generalized Distillation&lt;/a&gt; is accepted to IEEE Privacy-aware computing (PAC) conference, 2016. The use of privacy-sensitive patient data made us develop new algorithms for &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1707.01871.pdf&#34;&gt;Achieving Secure and Differentially Private Computations in Multiparty Settings&lt;/a&gt;. This paper is also accepted to PAC&#39;16. Lastly, we have developed algorithms that allow members to define data exchange policies in a privacy-preserving collaborative machine learning to dictate their data needs. Our paper &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1702.08342.pdf&#34;&gt;Curie: Policy-based Secure Data Exchange&lt;/a&gt; is accepted to ACM Conference on Data and Application Security and Privacy (CODASPY), 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;network-security&#34;&gt;Network Security&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this effort, we developed a framework that uses tamper-proof features to distinguish malware traffic from traffic generated by legitimate applications. Further, we characterize the evolution of malware evasion techniques over time by examining the behavior of 16 malware families. In particular, we highlight the difficulty of detecting malware that use traffic-shaping techniques to mimic legitimate traffic and demonstrated the challenges in malware detection through traffic analysis. Read more about our study &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Celik15_Milcom.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Celik11_CSET.pdf&#34;&gt;USENIX CSET&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Celik17_JDMS.pdf&#34;&gt;JDMS&lt;/a&gt; works, my co-authors and I also take a closer look at the experimentation artifacts of malware detection. For instance, we showed that malware detection systems produce unrealistically optimistic results that arise when they mix benign traffic in a domain with attack activity recorded in another domain and designed several statistical sampling algorithms for the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;science-of-security&#34;&gt;Science of Security&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am involved in Cyber-Security Collaborative Research Alliance (&lt;a href=&#34;http://cra.psu.edu/&#34;&gt;CSec CRA&lt;/a&gt;) with the Army Research Laboratory, Penn State, Carnegie Mellon, UC Riverside, UC Davis, and Indiana University. Our mandate is to develop a new science of security. As part of this effort, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on the foundation for representing of operational models for cybersecurity. I developed algorithms &lt;a href=&#34;http://wwwusers.di.uniroma1.it/~novella/myhome/Home_Page_di_Novella_Bartolini/milcom_2016.pdf&#34;&gt;to make optimal decisions in a cyber environment by modeling the current and future states of a cyber-operation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/activities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;journal-editorial-positions&#34;&gt;Journal Editorial Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024-Present, Co-moderator for cs.CR, the Cryptography and Security subject area in arXiv&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023-Present, Associate Editor, IEEE Transactions on Information Forensics and Security (T-IFS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chairco-chair&#34;&gt;Chair/Co-Chair&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, General Co-chair, IEEE/ACM Workshop on the Internet of Safe Things (co-located with IEEE  S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, General Co-chair, Symposium on Vehicle Security and Privacy (VehicleSec 2023) (co-located with NDSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, Program Co-chair, IEEE/ACM Workshop on the Internet of Safe Things (co-located with CPS-IoT Week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, Program Co-chair, AutoSec (Automotive and Autonomous Vehicle Security) Workshop (co-located with NDSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, Workshop Co-Chair, IEEE Conference on Communications and Network Security (CNS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, Session Chair SecureComm Conference (Web Security)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;technical-program-committee&#34;&gt;Technical Program Committee&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024, 2023, 2022, 2021, USENIX Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024, 2023 IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024, 2023, 2022, NDSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024, 2023, 2021 CCS (ML and Security Track, and Hardware, Side Channels, and Cyber-Physical Systems Track)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2024, 2023, Security and Privacy in Wireless and Mobile Networks (WiSec)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, Secure and Trustworthy Machine Learning (SATML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, 2019, CCS Workshop on the Internet of Things Security and Privacy (IoT S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, IEEE SmartGridComm (Security and Privacy track)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, IEEE Secure Development Conference (SecDev)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, Workshop on Internet of Safe Things (co-located with IEEE S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021, ACSAC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021, Workshop on Internet of Safe Things (co-located with IEEE S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021, European Symposium on Research in Computer Security (ESORICS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, SecureComm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, Workshop on Trustworthy ML (co-located with ICLR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, European Symposium on Research in Computer Security (ESORICS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, 2019, Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence (UAI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, IEEE Computer Security Foundations Symposium (CSF)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, CCS Workshop on the Internet of Things Security and Privacy (IoT S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, MILCOM 2019 (Track 3 - Cyber Security and Trusted Computing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, Workshop on ML for Security and Cryptography (co-located with IEEE PIMRC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, ASIA Conference on Computer and Communications Security (ASIACCS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, NIPS Workshop on Security in Machine Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, CCS Poster/Demonstration Session&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, Privacy-Aware Computing Symposium (IEEE PAC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, Internet of Things Security and Privacy Workshop (IoT S&amp;amp;P) (co-located with CCS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, Cyber-Physical Systems Security Workshop (CPS-Sec) (co-located with CNS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, Conference for Military Communications (MILCOM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;journal-and-external-reviewer&#34;&gt;Journal and External Reviewer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, 2017, IEEE Transactions on Information Forensics and Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, 2019, IEEE Security &amp;amp; Privacy Magazine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2023, 2022, 2018, 2017, ACM Computing Surveys (CSUR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, 2019, IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, INFOCOM (External Reviewer on Fuzzing and Explainable AI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2022, IEEE Transactions on Software Engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020, 2019, IEEE Transactions on Dependable and Secure Computing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, ACM Transactions on Internet of Things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, 2018, USENIX Security Symposium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, 2018, 2017, IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (S&amp;amp;P)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, ACM Conference on Computer and Communications Security (CCS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, Conference on Decision and Game Theory for Security (GameSec)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, Neural Information Processing Systems (NIPS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, IEEE Security and Privacy Magazine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, Neural Processing Letters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, Computers Open Access Journal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, Journal of Network and Computer Applications (JNCA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!---
	
### Teaching Experience
* [CMPSC 311](http://www.patrickmcdaniel.org/teach.html): System Programming (with Prof. Patrick McDaniel) (Fall 2016)
* [CMPSC 443](http://www.patrickmcdaniel.org/teach.html): Introduction to Computer Security (with Prof. Patrick McDaniel) (Spring 2017, Fall 2018)
* CSE 597: Security and Privacy of Machine Learning (with Prof. Patrick McDaniel and Nicolas Papernot) (Fall 2016)
* CSE 597: Advanced Topics in the Security and Privacy of Machine Learning (with Prof. Patrick McDaniel and Nicolas Papernot) (Spring 2017)

#### Guest lecturer
* CSE 597: Wireless and Mobile Security (Fall 2017)
* CSE 543: Computer Security (Fall 2018)


### Invited Talks/Presentations

##### Automated IoT Security and Privacy Analysis
* November 2018: Automated IoT Security and Privacy Analysis, University of Florida (host: [Dr. Kevin Butler](https://cise.ufl.edu/~butler/) and [Dr. Patrick Traynor](https://www.cise.ufl.edu/~traynor/))
* October 2018: Automated IoT Security and Privacy Analysis, Worcester Polytechnic Institute (host: [Dr. Berk Sunar](https://www.wpi.edu/people/faculty/sunar))
* September 2018: Automated IoT Security and Privacy Analysis, Northeastern University (host: [Dr. Engin Kirda](http://www.ccs.neu.edu/home/ek/))
* August 2018: Automated IoT Safety and Security Analysis, [USENIX Security Lightning Talks](https://www.usenix.org/conference/usenixsecurity18/activities#lightning) 
* August 2018: Program Analysis of IoT Applications for Security and Privacy at [USENIX Security HotSec&#39;18](https://www.usenix.org/conference/hotsec18) (**The most amusing talk award**)
* April 2018: Recent Research on IoT Security and Privacy, Penn State University (host: [Dr. Senchun Zhu](http://www.cse.psu.edu/~sxz16/), CSE 597: Wireless and Mobile Security class)
* April 2018: Recent Research on IoT Security and Privacy, Penn State University (CMPSC 443: Computer Security class)
* March 2018: Automated IoT Privacy and Security Analysis, [Army Research Laboratory](https://www.arl.army.mil/www/default.cfm) (host: Dr. Ed Colbert)
* September 2017: Sensitive Information Tracking in Commodity IoT, [Great Lakes Security Day 2017, RIT](https://www.rit.edu/cybersecurity/great-lakes-security-day-2017) (host: [Dr. Matthew Wright](https://sites.google.com/site/matthewkwright/))
* June 2017: Automated IoT Safety and Security Analysis, University of California, Davis 

##### Generating Machine Learning Models under Privileged Information
* December 2016: Recent Research Topics in Security and Privacy, [Istanbul Technical University](http://www.bb.itu.edu) (host: [Dr. Sema Oktug](http://web.itu.edu.tr/~oktug/))
* December 2016: Detection under Privileged Information, [Florida International University](https://csl.fiu.edu/) (host: [Dr. Selcuk Uluagac](http://web.eng.fiu.edu/selcuk/))
* August 2015: Detection under Privileged Information for Security, Penn State University, [Institute for Networking and Security Research](http://insr.psu.edu/)
* May 2016: Detection under Privileged Information for Security, Indiana University 
* August 2015: Detection under Privileged Information, [Vencore Labs](https://www.vencorelabs.com/) (Intern presentation)

##### Security and Privacy of Machine Learning
* December 2018: CSE 543 Computer Security, Penn State University (Adversarial Machine Learning lecture) (host: [Dr. Trent Jaeger](http://www.cse.psu.edu/~trj1/))
* July 2017: Convolutional Neural Networks for Secure Code, [VMware Cambridge Office](https://www.vmware.com/) (VMware CTO Office Presentation) 
* August 2017: Deep Learning for Analyzing VMware Software, [VMware Cambridge Office](https://www.vmware.com/) (VMware Intern Presentation) 
* July 2016: College of Engineering Symposium, Penn State University

##### Malware Detection and Modeling Operations in Cyberspace
* March 2016: Malware Traffic Detection using Tamper Resistant Features, [Army Research Laboratory](https://www.arl.army.mil/www/default.cfm) (host: Dr. Ananthram Swami)
* March 2016: Mapping Sample Scenarios to Operational Models in Cyber Environments, [George Mason University](https://www2.gmu.edu/) (host: [Dr. Sushil Jajodia](http://csis.gmu.edu/jajodia/))
* August 2015: Malware Experimentation in a Testbed Environment, Vencore Labs
* June 2015: Malware Detection through tamper-proof features, University of California, Riverside 


### Awards
* January 2019: Student Travel Award (The Network and Distributed System Security Symposium (NDSS 2019)) 
* August 2018: The most amusing talk award at [USENIX Security HoTSec&#39;18](https://www.usenix.org/conference/hotsec18/summit-program)
* August 2018: Best Paper Award (14th EAI International Conference on Security and Privacy in Communication Networks (SecureComm 2018))
* May 2018: Student Travel Award (ACM ASIA Conference on Information, Computer and Communications Security (ACM ASIACCS 2018)) 
* March 2018: Best demo award (Sensitive Information Tracking in Commodity IoT, [Florida Institute for Cybersecurity Research (FICS) Research Annual Conference on Cybersecurity](http://fics.institute.ufl.edu/poster-demo-winners-at-the-fics-annual-conference-on-cybersecurity/))
* July 2015: Student Travel Award (Military Communications Conference (MILCOM))
* August 2015 and 2017: PSU Summer Tuition Assistance Program (STAP) Fellowship


### Internships
* 2017 (Summer): Software Engineer, VMware CTO Office, Greater Boston Area (Managers: Ronn Mann and [Josh Simons](https://octo.vmware.com/author/josh_simons/))
* 2015 (Summer): Research Associate, Vencore Labs, New Jersey (Managers: Dr. Ritu Chadha and [Dr. Rauf Izmailov](https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=eA2qnCYAAAAJ&amp;hl=en))


--&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/students/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;current-students&#34;&gt;Current Students:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ozgurozmen.github.io&#34;&gt;M. Ozgur Ozmen&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com.eg/citations?user=rdIzDcEAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en&#34;&gt;Reham Aburas&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arjunaru97.github.io/&#34;&gt;Arjun Arunasalam&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://raymond-muller.netlify.app/&#34;&gt;Raymond Muller&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chandms.github.io/&#34;&gt;Chandrika Mukherjee&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Ananth Shreekumar&lt;/a&gt; (PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD co-advising:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ruoyu.bio/&#34;&gt;Ruoyu Song&lt;/a&gt; (PhD) (co-advised with Antonio Bianchi)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Doguhan Yeke&lt;/a&gt; (PhD) (co-advised with Antonio Bianchi)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Msc Students: Devin Ersoy, Jyun-Jhu Syu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate Student Researchers: Xueyuan Cao&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;past-phd-students&#34;&gt;Past PhD Students:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://habiba-farrukh.github.io/&#34;&gt;Habiba Farrukh&lt;/a&gt; (2023) (now Assistant Professor in the Department of Computer Science at the University of California, Irvine.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kimhyungsub.github.io/&#34;&gt;Hyungsub Kim&lt;/a&gt; (2023) (now Postdoctoral Researcher in Department of Computer Science at Purdue University) (co-advised with Dongyan Xu and Antonio Bianchi)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://khaled-alsharif.github.io/&#34;&gt;Khaled Serag&lt;/a&gt; (2023) (now Research Scientist at Qatar Computing Research Institute) (co-advised with Dongyan Xu)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cssaheel.github.io/&#34;&gt;Abdulellah Alsaheel&lt;/a&gt; (2023) (now private Security Consultant) (co-advised with Dongyan Xu)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;supervised-msc-students&#34;&gt;Supervised Msc Students&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ananth Shreekumar, 2023 &amp;ndash; now PhD under my supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jyun-Jhu Syu, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yufan Chen, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rwitam Bandyopadhyay, 2023 &amp;ndash; now at Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jackson Bizjak, 2022 &amp;ndash; now at NVIDIA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gaurav Jadhav, 2022&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://yslin013.github.io/&#34;&gt;Yi-Shan Lin&lt;/a&gt; (Msc) &amp;ndash; now at Google&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mastermjr.com&#34;&gt;Michael Reeves&lt;/a&gt; [Thesis: Investigating Escape Vulnerabilities in Container Runtimes] &amp;ndash; now at Sandia Labs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Siddharth Divi [Thesis: Unifying Distillation with Personalization in Federated Learning] &amp;ndash; now at Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://basavesh.github.io&#34;&gt;Basavesh Shivakumar&lt;/a&gt; (Msc) &amp;ndash; now PhD at MPI-SP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Akhil Sai Bandarupalli (Msc) &amp;ndash; Now PhD at Purdue CS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://zhanfuyang.com/&#34;&gt;Zhanfu Yang&lt;/a&gt; (Msc) &amp;ndash; now PhD at Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliz Tekcan (Msc), graduated Fall 22 &amp;ndash; now at Vestel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abhinav Gupta (Msc), graduated Fall 22 &amp;ndash; now at Facebook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abhishek Shah (Msc), graduated Fall 22 &amp;ndash; now at Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aniket Nare (Msc), graduated Fall 22 &amp;ndash; now at Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;undergraduate-researchers&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Researchers&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jason Perry &amp;ndash; now at Google&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://haozheee.github.io/&#34;&gt;Haozhe Zhou&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; now PhD at CMU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://andrewcchu.github.io&#34;&gt;Andrew Chu&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; now PhD at UChicago&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;William Carter Bell (Junior, Data Science)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anirudh Giridhar (Junior, Purdue Computer Science minor in Mathematics and Statistics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kaushik Ramachandran (Senior, Computer Science)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yizhen (Yuen) Yuan, (Junior, Purdue CS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ishan Kaul (Senior, Purdue Computer Science)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sidhartha Agrawal (Sophomore, Purdue Computer Science minor in Mathematics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yuxuan Yang (Junior, Purdue Computer Science minor in Mathematics and Economics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rafael Zhu (Freshman, Purdue Computer Science)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nail Tarcan Gul (Senior, Purdue Computer Science)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;external-research-interns&#34;&gt;External Research Interns&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blaise Swartwood (SROP intern program, junior, Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furkan Goksel (GoBoiler Internship Program, Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kerem Ors (GoBoiler Internship Program, Msc, Computer Science, Sabanci University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yigit Varli (Summer Intern, Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bharat Chandra (Senior, Vellore Institute of Technology, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anirudh Gupta and Mohit Thakur (Junior, Computer Science, IIT Delhi, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mohit Thakur (Junior, Computer Science, IIT Delhi, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Berk Aydogmus (Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yahya Sungur (Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burak Ucar (Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Berkin Kerim Konar (Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kerem Serttas, (Senior, Computer Science, Middle East Technical University, Online)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/fullteaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/fullteaching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;cs-426-computer-security-undergraduate-syllabuscs426cs426pdf-spring-23&#34;&gt;CS 426: Computer Security (Undergraduate) &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/cs426/CS426.pdf&#34;&gt;[Syllabus]&lt;/a&gt; [Spring 23]&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This introductory undergraduate course focuses on the principles and foundations of building secure computer systems, security best practices, and security failures in existing and emerging computer networks and systems. The course covers four key topic areas: basics of cryptography and crypto protocols, network security, systems security, and privacy. Students successfully completing this class will be able to understand and assess security threats, become familiar with security engineering best practices, write better software, protocols, and systems, and have rudimentary skills in security research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;cs-390-great-issues-in-computer-science-syllabuscs390cs390pdf-fall-23&#34;&gt;CS 390: Great Issues In Computer Science &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/cs390/CS390.pdf&#34;&gt;[Syllabus]&lt;/a&gt; [Fall 23]&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this interdisciplinary undergraduate course, I teach the evolving landscape of professional and ethical challenges in computing, with a particular focus on its societal implications. I cover established topics such as algorithmic bias, fairness, and accountability, but also the ethical frontiers of emerging technologies, e.g.,  artificial intelligence and the increasingly intertwined digital-physical world with cyber-physical systems. Through in-depth discussions of real-world examples and critical readings, students learn about algorithmic design choices, data collection and use ethics in AI,  societal inequalities that autonomous systems exacerbate, and the legal frameworks struggling to keep pace with such technological advancements. In this way, students are equipped with the critical thinking skills and contextual knowledge necessary to navigate the dynamic landscape of emerging computing platforms and become responsible citizens of the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;cs-529-security-analytics-graduate-syllabuscs529contentsyllabuscs529pdf-fall-22-fall-21-fall-20-fall-19&#34;&gt;CS 529: Security Analytics (Graduate) &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/cs529/content/syllabus/CS529.pdf&#34;&gt;[Syllabus]&lt;/a&gt; [Fall 22] [Fall 21] [Fall 20] [Fall 19]&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This graduate-level course will provide students with materials to discuss the intersection of two ubiquitous concepts: Security and Machine Learning. The course is structured in two parts: (1) Machine Learning for Security and (2) Security of Machine Learning Systems. The focus of the first part will be on building a principled understanding of key learning algorithms and techniques, and their applications within the security domain, as well as general questions related to analyzing and handling datasets. The first part will provide students with the necessary background to understand the second half of the course. The second part covers recently discovered security implications of deploying machine learning algorithms in the physical realm. Students will learn about attacks against computer systems leveraging machine learning algorithms, as well as defense techniques to mitigate such attacks during learning and inference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;cs-590-iotcps-security-graduate-syllabuscs592s22cs592iotcpspdf-spring-22-spring-20&#34;&gt;CS 590: IoT/CPS Security (Graduate) &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/cs592S22/CS592IoTCPS.pdf&#34;&gt;[Syllabus]&lt;/a&gt; [Spring 22] [Spring 20]&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, we will study the latest research in the design of Internet of Things (IoT) and Cyber-Physical Systems (CPS) and methods for securing them. The course will provide foundations of safety and security of IoT/CPS and covers the topics of policy verification, approaches for designing safe and secure systems, techniques for detecting problems in conventional IoT/CPS design and repairing such problems. Example topics include the security of voice-controlled devices, IoT applications, edge computing, industrial control systems, and autonomous vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IoT Security and Privacy:&lt;/strong&gt; From time to time I receive emails asking how to start studying IoT security and privacy. I and my colleague, Xiaolei Wang, have grouped a collection of papers that we recommend reading for those interested in IoT security and privacy (including trigger-action platforms and voice-controlled devices). If you have any suggestions, please send a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Beerkay/IoTResearch&#34;&gt;pull request&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;first-depth-study-on-iot-security&#34;&gt;First depth study on IoT Security&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, IEEE S&amp;amp;P, &lt;a href=&#34;http://iotsecurity.eecs.umich.edu/img/Fernandes_SmartThingsSP16.pdf&#34;&gt;Security Analysis of Emerging Smart Home Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;sensitive-information-flow-tracking&#34;&gt;Sensitive Information Flow Tracking&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, USENIX Security, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity16/sec16_paper_fernandes.pdf&#34;&gt;FlowFence: Practical Data Protection for Emerging IoT Application Frameworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, USENIX Security, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity18/sec18-celik.pdf&#34;&gt;Sensitive Information Tracking in Commodity IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;access-control&#34;&gt;Access Control&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, NDSS, &lt;a href=&#34;https://amir.rahmati.com/dl/ndss17/ContexIoT_NDSS17.pdf&#34;&gt;ContexIoT: Towards Providing Contextual Integrity to Appified IoT Platforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, USENIX Security, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity17/sec17-tian.pdf&#34;&gt;SmartAuth: User-Centered Authorization for the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, Access Control Models, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.corelab.or.kr/Pubs/sacmat17_fact.pdf&#34;&gt;FACT: Functionality-centric Access Control System for IoT Programming Frameworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, USENIX Security, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity18/sec18-he.pdf&#34;&gt;Rethinking Access Control and Authentication for the Home Internet of Things (IoT)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, IEEE SecDev, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1801.04609&#34;&gt;Tyche: Risk-Based Permissions for Smart Home Platforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;safety-and-security-violation-identification-and-enforcement&#34;&gt;Safety and Security Violation Identification and Enforcement&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, NDSS, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Beerkay/IoTResearch&#34;&gt;IoTGuard: Dynamic Enforcement of Security and Safety Policy in Commodity IoT&lt;/a&gt;(will be available soon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, USENIX ATC, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/atc18/atc18-celik.pdf&#34;&gt;Soteria: Automated IoT Safety and Security Analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, CoNEXT, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1810.09551.pdf&#34;&gt;IoTSAN: Fortifying the Safety of IoT Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, CCS, &lt;a href=&#34;https://wding.people.clemson.edu/papers/ccs-2018iotmon.pdf&#34;&gt;On the Safety of IoT Device Physical Interaction Control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;vulnerability-mining&#34;&gt;Vulnerability Mining&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, NDSS, &lt;a href=&#34;http://web.cse.ohio-state.edu/~lin.3021/file/NDSS18b.pdf&#34;&gt;IoTFuzzer: Discovering Memory Corruptions in IoT Through App-based Fuzzing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;forensics&#34;&gt;Forensics&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, NDSS, &lt;a href=&#34;http://seclab.illinois.edu/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/wang2018fear.pdf&#34;&gt;Fear and Logging in the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;iot-malware&#34;&gt;IoT Malware&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, IEEE S&amp;amp;P, &lt;a href=&#34;https://rud.is/dl/ieee-sp-2018/435301a870.pdf&#34;&gt;Understanding Linux Malware&lt;/a&gt; *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;fault-detection-and-evaluation&#34;&gt;Fault Detection and Evaluation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, DSN, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8416520/&#34;&gt;Detecting and Identifying Faulty IoT Devices in Smart Home with Context Extraction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;privacy-inference-via-sensors-and-defenses&#34;&gt;Privacy Inference via Sensors and Defenses&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1808.02741&#34;&gt;Peek-a-Boo: I see your smart home activities even encrypted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1705.06809.pdf&#34;&gt;Closing the Blinds: Four Strategies for Protecting Smart Home Privacy from Network Observers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1808.07432.pdf&#34;&gt;A Developer-Friendly Library for Smart Home IoT Privacy Preserving Traffic Obfuscation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1708.05044.pdf&#34;&gt;Spying on the Smart Home Privacy Attacks and Defenses on Encrypted IoT Traffic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://faculty.washington.edu/lagesse/publications/HiddenSensorDetection.pdf&#34;&gt;Detecting Spies in IoT Systems using Cyber-Physical Correlation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;attacks-against-voice-control&#34;&gt;Attacks against Voice Control&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1805.01525.pdf&#34;&gt;Understanding and Mitigating the Security Risks of Voice-Controlled Third-Party Skills on Amazon Alexa and Google Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1808.05665.pdf&#34;&gt;Adversarial Attacks Against Automatic Speech Recognition Systems via Psychoacoustic Hiding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1801.08535.pdf&#34;&gt;CommanderSong: A Systematic Approach for Practical Adversarial Voice Recognition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1808.01947.pdf&#34;&gt;Nonsense Attacks on Google Assistant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;trigger-action-platform-measurement-and-security-analysis&#34;&gt;Trigger-action Platform Measurement and Security Analysis&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2016, CHI, &lt;a href=&#34;https://par.nsf.gov/servlets/purl/10026427&#34;&gt;Trigger-Action Programming in the Wild: An Analysis of 200,000 IFTTT Recipes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, WWW, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.andrew.cmu.edu/user/liminjia/research/papers/ifttt-info-flows-www2017.pdf&#34;&gt;Some Recipes Can Do More Than Spoil Your Appetite Analyzing the Security and Privacy Risks of IFTTT Recipes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1808.02741&#34;&gt;IFTTT vs. Zapier A Comparative Study of Trigger-Action Programming Frameworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, IMC, &lt;a href=&#34;https://conferences.sigcomm.org/imc/2017/papers/imc17-final41.pdf&#34;&gt;An Empirical Characterization of IFTTT Ecosystem, Usage, and Performance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, NDSS, &lt;a href=&#34;http://earlence.com/assets/papers/dtap_ndss18.pdf&#34;&gt;Decentralized Action Integrity for Trigger-Action IoT Platforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;iot-test-suite&#34;&gt;IoT Test Suite&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/IoTBench/IoTBench-test-suite&#34;&gt;IoTBench: A micro-benchmark suite to assess the effectiveness of tools designed for IoT apps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;iot-surveys&#34;&gt;IoT Surveys&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1809.06962.pdf&#34;&gt;Program Analysis of Commodity IoT Applications for Security and Privacy: Challenges and Opportunities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019, IEEE S&amp;amp;P, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.computer.org/csdl/proceedings/sp/2019/6660/00/666001a208-abs.html&#34;&gt;SoK: Security Evaluation of Home-Based IoT Deployments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1805.05853.pdf&#34;&gt;IoT Security: An End-to-End View and Case Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1807.11023.pdf&#34;&gt;A Survey of Machine and Deep Learning Methods for Internet of Things (IoT) Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1703.09809.pdf&#34;&gt;Understanding IoT Security Through the Data Crystal Ball: Where We Are Now and Where We Are Going to Be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2017, IEEE S&amp;amp;P Magazine, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1705.08522.pdf&#34;&gt;Internet of Things Security Research: A Rehash of Old Ideas or New Intellectual Challenges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, BlackHat, &lt;a href=&#34;https://i.blackhat.com/us-18/Thu-August-9/us-18-Costin-Zaddach-IoT-Malware-Comprehensive-Survey-Analysis-Framework-and-Case-Studies-wp.pdf&#34;&gt;IoT Malware: Comprehensive Survey, Analysis Framework and Case Studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018, arXiv, &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1802.02041.pdf&#34;&gt;A Survey on Sensor-based Threats to Internet-of-Things (IoT) Devices and Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/personal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sailing is my passion, whether it’s racing or cruising. I hold a professional sailing license in my country (equivalent to ASA 106, Advanced Coastal Cruising). I recently had a chance to sail on Charles River, Raritan Bay, and being at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sailboston.com/&#34;&gt;Sail Boston&#39;17&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt; 
&lt;img src=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/img/personal/sailCambridge.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt; 
&lt;img src=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/img/personal/orsa2.png&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I follow college sports closely. I am a huge fan of &lt;a href=&#34;https://purduesports.com/&#34;&gt;Boilermakers&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gopsusports.com/&#34;&gt;Nittany Lions&lt;/a&gt;, particularly when it comes to football and basketball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt; 
&lt;img src=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/img/personal/psu-game.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archieved News</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/newsarchieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/newsarchieve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;2024&#34;&gt;2024&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Congratulations to &lt;a href=&#34;https://raymond-muller.netlify.app/&#34;&gt;Raymond Muller&lt;/a&gt; on being selected for &lt;a href=&#34;https://risingstars.linklab.virginia.edu/2024/&#34;&gt;2024 CPS Rising Stars&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Congratulations to &lt;a href=&#34;https://raymond-muller.netlify.app/&#34;&gt;Ozgur Ozmen&lt;/a&gt; on receiving the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerias.purdue.edu/site/people/student_awards/diamond&#34;&gt;2024 CERIAS Diamond Award&lt;/a&gt; for his outstanding acadamic achievement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[ELLIIT Symposium Talk] I gave a talk at Lund University Sweden for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://elliit.se/news-and-events/focus-period-lund-2024/symposium/&#34;&gt;ELLIIT focus period&lt;/a&gt; Symposium on Security and Fault Tolerance of Cyber-Physical Systems. Thank you  Martina Maggio and Mikael Asplund  for hosting me!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CPSRC Seminar Talk] I gave a virtual talk at University of California Santa Cruz Baskin School of Engineering, Cyber-Physical Systems Research Center (CPSRC). Thank you Ricardo Sanfelice, Alvaro Cardenas, Daniel Fremont for hosting me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Congratulations to &lt;a href=&#34;https://arjunaru97.github.io/&#34;&gt;Arjun Arunasalam&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ruoyu.bio/&#34;&gt;Ruoyu Song&lt;/a&gt; on receiving the Graduate Teaching Award.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE S&amp;amp;P 24] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2024SensorSpoofingOakland.pdf&#34;&gt;A Systematic Study of Physical Sensor Attack Hardness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE S&amp;amp;P 24] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2024WearOSOakland.pdf&#34;&gt;Wear’s my Data? Understanding the Cross-Device Runtime Permission Model in Wearables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 24] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2024ATTUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;ATTention Please! An Investigation of the App Tracking Transparency Permission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 24] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2024ToxicContentUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Understanding the Security and Privacy Implications of Online Toxic Content on Refugees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 24] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2024DropshippingNDDS.pdf&#34;&gt;The Dark Side of E-commerce: Dropshipping Abuse as a Business Model&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[VehicleSec] &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndss-symposium.org/ndss2024/co-located-events/vehiclesec/&#34;&gt;General Co-chair - Symposium on Vehicle Security and Privacy  (VehicleSec) 2024&lt;/a&gt; will be co-located with NDSS at San Diego on Feb 26, 2024 &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/vehiclesec_conf&#34;&gt;Follow @VehicleSec2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[SafeThings] &lt;a href=&#34;https://safe-things-2024.github.io/&#34;&gt;PC Co-chair - IEEE/ACM Workshop on the Internet of Safe Things 2024&lt;/a&gt; will be co-located with IEEE S&amp;amp;P Sympoisum on Mar 23, 2024 &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/SafeThings2024&#34;&gt;Follow @SafeThings2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;2023&#34;&gt;2023&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m so proud of my first Ph.D. student, &lt;a href=&#34;https://habiba-farrukh.github.io/&#34;&gt;Habiba Farrukh&lt;/a&gt;, who successfully defended her thesis. Habiba will join UC Irvine as an Assistant Professor in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ics.uci.edu/&#34;&gt;Department of Computer Science&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Habiba!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[ACSAC 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023LLMMisconceptions.pdf&#34;&gt;Can Large Language Models Provide Security &amp;amp; Privacy Advice? Measuring the Ability of LLMs to Refute Misconceptions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CS Distinguished Speaker] I gave a talk at Univerity of Virginia. Thank you Tianhao Wang, Adwait Jog, and  David Evans for hosting me!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Keynote Speaker] I gave a talk at Workshop on Security and Privacy of Sensing Systems (Sensors S&amp;amp;P) colocated
with ACM SenSys. Thank you Luis Garcia and Fatima Anwar for hosting me!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[T-IFS] I joined the Associate Editor team of IEEE Transactions on Information Forensics and Security (T-IFS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited to be a part of the new &lt;a href=&#34;https://action.ucsb.edu/&#34;&gt;NSF AI Institute for Agent-based Cyber Threat Intelligence and OperatioN (ACTION)&lt;/a&gt; (led by Giovanni Vigna) with a great team of colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited to be part of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gsabusiness.com/news/education/83217/&#34;&gt;multi-university transportation center&lt;/a&gt; focusing on cybersecurity sponsored by the United States Department of Transportation (USDOT).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Congratulations to Raymond Muller on receiving the Graduate Teaching Award from Purdue Computer Science Department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Congratulations to Raymond Muller on receiving the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2023/purdue-cs-graduate-student-secures-x-force-fellowship.html?utm_source=sfmc&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=230713PurdueToday&amp;amp;utm_term=CS+graduate+student+secures+X-Force+Fellowship%2c+focusing+on+national+security+projects+&amp;amp;utm_id=761352&amp;amp;sfmc_id=0038c00002tusszAAA&#34;&gt;X-Force Fellowship&lt;/a&gt; through the National Security Innovation Network to solve national security problems in collaboration with the U.S. military.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023AceroUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Discovering Adversarial Driving Maneuvers against Autonomous Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023LocInUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;LocIn: Inferring Semantic Location from Spatial Maps in Mixed Realitys&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023ZBCANUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;ZBCAN: A Zero-Byte CAN Defense System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023PercepGuardUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;That Person Moves Like A Car: Misclassification Attack Detection for Autonomous Systems using Spatiotemporal Consistency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023PatchVerifUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;PatchVerif: Discovering Faulty Patches in Robotic Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE S&amp;amp;P 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023IoTCupidOakland.pdf&#34;&gt;One Key to Rule Them All: Secure Group Pairing for Heterogeneous IoT Devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[PETS 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023IStelanc.pdf&#34;&gt;iStelan: Disclosing Sensitive User Information by Mobile Magnetometer from Finger Touches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 23] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2023EvasionEVSNDDS.pdf&#34;&gt;Evasion Attacks and Defenses on Smart Home Physical Event Verification&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[VehicleSec 23] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2023SwarmPairingVehicleSec.pdf&#34;&gt;Rethinking Secure Pairing in Drone Swarms (Position Paper)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CFP] &lt;a href=&#34;https://safe-things-2023.github.io/&#34;&gt;Workshop Co-chair - Call for Papers: IEEE/ACM Workshop on the Internet of Safe Things 2023&lt;/a&gt;. SafeThings will happen with CPS-IoT Week at San Antonio on May 9, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CFP] &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndss-symposium.org/ndss2023/submissions/cfp-vehiclesec/&#34;&gt;Workshop Co-chair - Call for Papers: Inaugural Symposium on Vehicle Security and Privacy (VehicleSec) 2023&lt;/a&gt;. VehicleSec will happen with NDSS at San Diego on Feb 27, 2023 (Hybrid) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/vehiclesec_conf&#34;&gt;Follow @VehicleSec2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;2022&#34;&gt;2022&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[2022] I and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/homes/dxu/&#34;&gt;Prof. Xu&lt;/a&gt; received funding with the CISCO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Google ASPIRE 2022] Our team lead by I and &lt;a href=&#34;https://antoniobianchi.me/&#34;&gt;Prof. Bianchi&lt;/a&gt; won Google ASPIRE Award&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CCS 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2022IoTPhysicalCCS.pdf&#34;&gt;Discovering IoT Physical Channel Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CCS 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2022PhysicalHijackingCCS.pdf&#34;&gt;Physical Hijacking Attacks against Object Trackers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two papers and two demos are accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;AutoSec 22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two journal papers are accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;ACM Transcations on Internet of Things (TIOT) 22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE S&amp;amp;P 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/papers/Berkay2022PGPatchIEEESP.pdf&#34;&gt;PGPatch: Policy-Guided Logic Bug Patching for Robotic Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 22] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2022SaraUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;SARA: Secure Android Remote Authorization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndss-symposium.org/ndss2022/cfp-autosec-workshop/&#34;&gt;AutoSec (Automotive &amp;amp; Autonomous Vehicle Security) Workshop&lt;/a&gt; will be hosted with NDSS again in 2022! &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/autosec_conf?lang=en&#34;&gt;Follow @autosec_conf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve earned &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2022/career_celik.html&#34;&gt;NSF CAREER Award&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 22] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2022YoutubeUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Behind the Tube: Exploitative Monetization of Content on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;2021&#34;&gt;2021&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve received funding with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2021/purdue_rolls-royce_research2.html&#34;&gt;Rolls-Royce Cybersecurity Technology Research Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Google ASPIRE 2021] Our team lead by I and &lt;a href=&#34;https://antoniobianchi.me/&#34;&gt;Prof. Bianchi&lt;/a&gt; won &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2021/aspire_award.html&#34;&gt;Google ASPIRE Award&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[SafeThings 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021PenserSafethings.pdf&#34;&gt;On the Safety Implications of Misordered Events and Commands in IoT Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[PETS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021DaintPETS2021.pdf&#34;&gt;Real-time Analysis of Privacy-(un)aware IoT Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021PGFuzzNDSS.pdf&#34;&gt;PGFUZZ: Policy-Guided Fuzzing for Robotic Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021CanoxUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Exposing New Vulnerabilities of Error Handling Mechanism in CAN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021AtlasUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;ATLAS: A Sequence-based Learning Approach for Attack Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[KDD 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021XAITrojan.pdf&#34;&gt;What do you see? Evaluation of XAI Interpretability through Neural Backdoors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[ICML-FL 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021ICMLFLPersonalizedFL.pdf&#34;&gt;New Metrics to Evaluate the Performance and Fairness of Personalized FL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE SecDev 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021SecDevContainerSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Towards Improving Container Security by Preventing Runtime Escapes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021DuetNDSS.pdf&#34;&gt;Evading Voltage-Based Intrusion Detection on Automotive CAN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[UbiComp 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/berkay2021S3UbiComp.pdf&#34;&gt;S3: Side-channel Attack on Stylus Pencil Through Sensors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IoTDI 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021SentinelIoTDI.pdf&#34;&gt;Sentinel: A Robust IDS for IoT Networks Using Kernel-Level System Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=g1I269gAAAAJ&amp;amp;view_op=list_works&amp;amp;sortby=pubdate&#34;&gt;Google Scholar Page&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/purseclab&#34;&gt;Code and Datasets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://bibbase.org/show?bib=beerkay.github.io%2Fpapers%2FmyPublications.bib&amp;jsonp=1&amp;fullnames=1&amp;theme=side&amp;hidemenu=true&amp;commas=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!--
	&lt;script src=&#34;https://bibbase.org/show?bib=beerkay.github.io%2Fpapers%2FmyPublications.bib&amp;jsonp=1&amp;fullnames=1&amp;theme=side&amp;hidemenu=true&amp;commas=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;news&#34;&gt;News&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CCS 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;Discovering IoT Physical Channel Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[CCS 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;Physical Hijacking Attacks against Object Trackers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two papers and two demos are accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;AutoSec 22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two journal papers are accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;ACM Transcations on Internet of Things (TIOT) 22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE S&amp;amp;P 22] &lt;a href=&#34;https://beerkay.github.io/fullpublication&#34;&gt;PGPatch: Policy-Guided Logic Bug Patching for Robotic Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 22] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2022SaraUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;SARA: Secure Android Remote Authorization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndss-symposium.org/ndss2022/cfp-autosec-workshop/&#34;&gt;AutoSec (Automotive &amp;amp; Autonomous Vehicle Security) Workshop&lt;/a&gt; will be hosted with NDSS again in 2022! &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/autosec_conf?lang=en&#34;&gt;Follow @autosec_conf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve earned &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2022/career_celik.html&#34;&gt;NSF CAREER Award&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 22] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2022YoutubeUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Behind the Tube: Exploitative Monetization of Content on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve received funding with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2021/purdue_rolls-royce_research2.html&#34;&gt;Rolls-Royce Cybersecurity Technology Research Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our team lead by I and &lt;a href=&#34;https://antoniobianchi.me/&#34;&gt;Prof. Bianchi&lt;/a&gt; won &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.purdue.edu/news/articles/2021/aspire_award.html&#34;&gt;Google ASPIRE Award&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[SafeThings 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021PenserSafethings.pdf&#34;&gt;On the Safety Implications of Misordered Events and Commands in IoT Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[PETS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021DaintPETS2021.pdf&#34;&gt;Real-time Analysis of Privacy-(un)aware IoT Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021PGFuzzNDSS.pdf&#34;&gt;PGFUZZ: Policy-Guided Fuzzing for Robotic Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021CanoxUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Exposing New Vulnerabilities of Error Handling Mechanism in CAN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[USENIX Security 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021AtlasUSENIXSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;ATLAS: A Sequence-based Learning Approach for Attack Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[KDD 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021XAITrojan.pdf&#34;&gt;What do you see? Evaluation of XAI Interpretability through Neural Backdoors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[ICML-FL 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021ICMLFLPersonalizedFL.pdf&#34;&gt;New Metrics to Evaluate the Performance and Fairness of Personalized FL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IEEE SecDev 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021SecDevContainerSecurity.pdf&#34;&gt;Towards Improving Container Security by Preventing Runtime Escapes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[NDSS 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021DuetNDSS.pdf&#34;&gt;Evading Voltage-Based Intrusion Detection on Automotive CAN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[UbiComp 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/berkay2021S3UbiComp.pdf&#34;&gt;S3: Side-channel Attack on Stylus Pencil Through Sensors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[IoTDI 21] &lt;a href=&#34;papers/Berkay2021SentinelIoTDI.pdf&#34;&gt;Sentinel: A Robust IDS for IoT Networks Using Kernel-Level System Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/courses/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/slides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://beerkay.github.io/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beerkay.github.io/project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
